Because helping others
eventually ends up being good for me.
Run.
You.
You'll just get in my way,
so get out of here, will you?
Demon Slayer: Swordsmith Village Arc
Episode 4: Thank You, Tokito
Even if I cut what appears to be the neck,
it's not disintegrating, but regenerating.
Then, it must be that type.
It was getting power from the vase.
Just as I thought. It was created
by some Blood Demon Art.
Thank you!
I thought I was gonna die! Really die!
I was so scared!
I was wrong to call you kelp head!
I'm sorry!
Kelp head? You mean me?
I'm sorry! I hated you!
I don't have time for this.
I'm going,
so you can do whatever you want.
Wait.
Kanamori is being attacked.
I was also attacked
when I came out to get help.
Haganezuka is working day and night
to polish and restore a sword.
If his work stops even a little bit,
it won't be good anymore.
Please, help us.
I beg you.
Well, I…
You will definitely regain yourself,
Muichiro.
I know, you must be confused.
But for now, just think about surviving.
As long as you are alive,
it will work out somehow.
Your lost memories will return.
No need to worry.
Don't ignore this opportunity.
Trivial things will spark something.
And then,
it will clear the fog inside your head.
Slow down a little!
Don't go so fast!
You'll bite your tongue if you talk.
Is this the right decision?
By doing this, I won't be able
to protect the entire village.
No, I can do this.
I'm a member of the Corps
recognized by the Master,
Muichiro Tokito, the Mist Hashira.
Crap!
I cut it. What should I do?
It will multiply.
JOY
FOUR - UPPER
Both have the same name?
I see. I get it now.
The attacks are less powerful.
They probably won't get
infinitely stronger with every split.
ANGER
I saw letters in their mouths.
It's four human emotions.
It's likely those four are the strongest.
JOY
And if they split any further,
they're less powerful.
Behind me.
I have to defeat
at least one of them.
And get back to Nezuko and Genya.
The demon mouth I stabbed disappeared?
I knew it. The split won't go any further.
How do you like my claws?
With this speed and sharpness,
they can even crush a diamond!
You should be trembling.
Let me enjoy your blood splashing.
You too.
How dare you!
I want to get back
to Nezuko and Genya quickly.
But how?
Nezuko, hang in there!
Hang in there a little longer, girl.
Hey. What's wrong?
Rip her limbs off right away.
You're just getting me angry.
Don't interfere. This girl is mine.
You and Aizetsu go somewhere else.
Karaku, let me finish her off.
I can't pull out my spear.
Your opponent is me.
How can you get shot, Aizetsu?
How infuriating.
You fool.
Shit! It's getting pulled out.
It's too sad that you won't die instantly.
DEMON SLAYER: SWORDSMITH VILLAGE ARC
I aimed for a vital spot
so he could die quickly.
It didn't work
because he held on to my spear.
But now he will surely die.
What? Is he chanting the Amida Sutra?
How devout is he.
Isn't he still alive?
Crush his head, Aizetsu!
I know, so stop yelling, will you?
It makes me sad.
I'll cut your neck as many times
as it takes to kill you worms!
Shit! There's no way
to dodge this lightning.
That Khakkhara-wielding bastard!
What the hell is this guy?
Why won't he die even though Aizetsu
has inflicted a fatal blow?
Hey! That guy looks more fun
to be playing with.
I'm done with you, girl.
Sekido.
After I rip off this demon girl's limbs,
stab her with your Khakkhara.
Then stun her with lightning
so she won't move.
That was my intention from the start.
The heck is with her kicking power?
What are you doing, you fool?
So fast. His speed has increased.
Although I want to get back quickly,
and the building where they are
is right over there…
What should I do? Think!
Right.
If I can't defeat him here and now--
But wait,
the situation might get even worse.
I don't know. I have no idea.
Don't hesitate.
I just have to do it anyway.
Nezuko, Genya,
don't die on me. I'll be there soon.
I guess he's dead already.
How are you still alive?
What…
What the hell are you?
You wanna know?
My name is Genya Shinazugawa.
Make sure you remember it.
It's the name of the man…
…who's gonna kill you!
Nezuko and Genya are
in the building right there.
I need to get there quickly.
Don't misjudge the direction.
I'll take advantage
of his flight and momentum
to save Nezuko and Genya
as soon as possible.
Why are you running?
Where is your earlier smugness?
Just as I thought, he's light.
Otherwise, he wouldn't be able
to fly around with wings that size.
I can do this!
Nezuko! Genya!
Not only Karaku, but Urogi too.
What are they doing?
Nezuko!
Stop it!
So infuriating. You all make me angry.
Urogi's foot?
Since it has the same cells as mine,
the lightning won't pass through it.
This boy has good instincts.
When he broke into this room,
he cut Urogi's foot in an instant.
He's a quick thinker in a fight.
I can't cut him with just one hand.
Tongue. Aim for his tongue.
If their tongues are damaged,
these demons will regenerate more slowly.
Good. I can pull this out.
ANGER
You'll pay for this.
Crap. He's already recovered.
It stopped?
Nezuko.
What an insolent Demon Art.
Incredible.
Nezuko's blood is quite effective.
Nezuko!
That looks fun.
Let me join you guys!
This pressure,
it's crushing my body.
It's time for the finishing blow.
We're under attack!
It's the demons!
Get up.
We're under attack! Protect our village!
Hurry.
The village is in danger.
Save the villagers as quickly as possible.
I have to hurry, pronto.
Everyone in the village is in danger.
But surprisingly,
the village of the swordsmiths is so close
to the district I'm in charge of.
Hurry. The village is
on the brink of collapse.
All right. I'll do my best.
DEMON SLAYER: SWORDSMITH VILLAGE ARC
NO. 4
Long time no see!
Now it's time for a Kimetsu Academy story!
My name is Mitsuri Kanroji, 19 years old.
My dream is to make people
around the world happy with my paintings.
Hey. Will you listen?
When does the man
who will make me happy appear?
No one is going to love you.
Huh?
Look, your hair is pink, you're a glutton
and as powerful as a gorilla.
Isn't that why you paint?
That's your way of life.
You're right.
No other choice than to paint.
Only my paintings
can make everyone happy.
SHE'S POPULAR WITH MEN,
BUT SHE IS UNAWARE OF IT
Next up on "Episode 5: Bright Red Blade."
TO BE CONTINUED
I also want a boyfriend, after all.